<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Lnxknl</title>
  
  <subtitle>平凡伟大</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://lnxknl.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2022-07-03T14:48:47.155Z</updated>
  <id>https://lnxknl.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>lnxknl</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>life record</title>
    <link href="https://lnxknl.github.io/2022/embrace_life/"/>
    <id>https://lnxknl.github.io/2022/embrace_life/</id>
    <published>2022-07-03T14:48:47.155Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-03T14:48:47.155Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>端午假期，难得的休闲时间，三天休假，昨天躺了一天，今日上午磨蹭，计划出去玩。于是午后就准备东西出门了</p><a id="more"></a><p>离家到深圳工作已近四月有余了，生活好似发生了天翻地覆的变化。在公司附近租了个小房间，只有一张床，或只能放下一张床，后自己添了个小冰箱。今日公司初期，并不很忙，平日也会自己做个饭吃，冰箱也常常放满了些要准备做的菜。满满的，随着项目越做越深，加班也越来越多了，先是晚上加班，慢慢周六也开始加班了。自己也几乎每顿都是在快餐店解决。近月来，冰箱已近没有添置过准备做的菜了。大多数时候，下班已近时晚上10或11点了。回到住处，便是摊倒在床上休息片刻，在然后看看书，看看一些关注的UP更新的视频，到12点或12点半左右，便睡去。<br>如果生活总是一成不变的，那将会变得像一潭死水。平日里的假期，除去周六加班，就一天休息，那大多数都是休息，看会书，看些视频便过去了。这次假期，第一天也和往常一样度过。昨天休息了一天，今日便想出门走走，呼吸一下新鲜空气。便提了个包，骑着自行车出去了。本有规划路线，但想想核酸结果还每出来，如果骑远了，若再骑回来，那也太累了。便无目的的在附近7,8公里骑走了。戴了墨镜，可是太阳太晒了，又穿的短袖。只是想着边骑边看看，戴了墨镜，又不注意太阳光。到骑回来时，才猛然发现双臂都被晒成暗红色了。骑车出去，看看形形色色的行人。久在电脑面前，敲着机械的键盘，看着一行行的代码，闲适也是看着些UP的视频。出去走走，接触些真实世界里的事事物物。前段时间，看了看瓦尔澄湖，其实早就了解过了。但还是想看看，一个孤独的人是如何面对孤独的，我们都是一个一个真实的人，现实世界里总是将纷杂的事物往你眼睛里塞，而我们又无法逃避这些东西，只能像一个人在人流中被夹裹着被带去无名的地方。<br>我骑着车，看着来往的路人。有骑着车，匆匆忙忙赶着路，有牵着手的情侣，有边走边踢球的少年，有骑车回家的学生。<br>总结一句，这次出来，主要是锻炼一下，这几个月来，都没怎么运动。又不想只是单纯的跑步，就选择了骑车。接下来的一段时间，多看些书，增强下专业技能，好在岗位上应付的过来。<br>时 2022年06月04号记</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;端午假期，难得的休闲时间，三天休假，昨天躺了一天，今日上午磨蹭，计划出去玩。于是午后就准备东西出门了&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
      <category term="life" scheme="https://lnxknl.github.io/tags/life/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>英语文章生成</title>
    <link href="https://lnxknl.github.io/2022/aritcle_generate_ky/"/>
    <id>https://lnxknl.github.io/2022/aritcle_generate_ky/</id>
    <published>2022-07-03T14:37:46.159Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-03T14:37:46.159Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>比照一篇考研英语范文，通过输入关联词，生成一篇文章。</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="英文原文"><a href="#英文原文" class="headerlink" title="英文原文"></a>英文原文</h2><p>Some athletes and entertainers earn millions of dollars annually. In contrast, an elementary school teacher, on average, probably makes less than $35,000 a year. I think the fact that this difference is commonplaces is a sign of our society’s misplaced values. It shows that we put more importance on entertaining our children than on educating them. It seems that the careers that are the least values in our society often are those that are the most important.</p><p>Why is this so? The market determines who gets paid what. Teachers are paid by tax dollars. Sports teams make hundreds of millions of dollars every year. These teams earn fabulous profits from radio and television rights, as well as everything sold at the concessions stands. The same is true of movies. They are produced by studios that make huge profits annually. These enterprises can afford to pay their entertainers and sports figures huge salaries, because those athletes and film stars draw people to the entertainment.</p><p>Why are we willing to pay so much to see a ball game or a movie, but not for a good teacher? Maybe it’s because we want distraction; we want to be entertained. Maybe it’s because we think of education as a right, which entertainment seems like a luxury. We expect to pay for our luxuries.</p><p>It’s not that I begrudge the players and entertainers their huge salaries. Most of them have very short careers. Athletes may be too old in their early 30s. Many of them gamble early in their lives on making it big in the sports or entertainment world, and deny themselves a good education. They have little chance of a stable career, so they need to earn enough money to support them for a long time. On the other hand, most of us aren’t going to earn $10 million in a lifetime of work. So it’s hard to sympathize with people who do.</p><p>We have to ask ourselves: who really give the most value to society?</p><h2 id="生成文章"><a href="#生成文章" class="headerlink" title="生成文章"></a>生成文章</h2><p>文章标题: argument on wheather to use the new or old style</p><p>Some of the code in this file is based on the old style.<br>In contrast, the new style is based on the new style.<br>on average, the new style is faster.<br>I think the fact that the new style is faster is a good reason<br>It shows that the new style is more flexible.<br>It seems that the new style is more flexible.<br>Why is the new style more flexible?<br>The people who wrote the new style are more experienced.<br>as well as the people who wrote the old style.<br>the same is true for the people who use the new style.<br>They are more experienced.<br>These people are more experienced.<br>Because the new style is more flexible.<br>Why are the people who use the new style more experienced?<br>but not for the people who wrote the new style.<br>maybe the people who wrote the old style are more experienced.<br>which is not true.<br>we expect the people who wrote the old style are more experienced.<br>It’s not that the people who wrote the old style are more experienced.<br>Most of them are not.<br>Many of them are not.<br>and deny that the people who wrote the old style are more experienced.<br>so they are not.<br>On the other hand, the people who use the new style are more experienced.<br>So they are more experienced.<br>We have to admit that the people who wrote the old style are more experienced.<br>But we have to deny that the people who use the new style are more experienced.<br>The people who wrote the old style are more experienced.<br>The people who use the new style are more experienced.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;比照一篇考研英语范文，通过输入关联词，生成一篇文章。&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>汇编练习</title>
    <link href="https://lnxknl.github.io/2022/assemly/"/>
    <id>https://lnxknl.github.io/2022/assemly/</id>
    <published>2022-07-03T14:37:46.159Z</published>
    <updated>2022-07-03T14:37:46.159Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>复习一下汇编和gdb的使用</p><a id="more"></a><h2 id="编译指令"><a href="#编译指令" class="headerlink" title="编译指令"></a>编译指令</h2><p>nasm -f elf -g -F stabs hello.o hello.asm</p><p>ld -m elf_i386 -o hello hello.o</p><h2 id="调试"><a href="#调试" class="headerlink" title="调试"></a>调试</h2><p>gdb hello</p><p><img src="../../src/img/asm.png" alt="汇编"></p><blockquote><p>参考资料：<a href="https://asmtutor.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">asmtutor</a></p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;复习一下汇编和gdb的使用&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
    
      <category term="汇编" scheme="https://lnxknl.github.io/tags/%E6%B1%87%E7%BC%96/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
